Okay, so Anita Baker, Anita Baker was supposed to do a show at 7 p.m. on Mother's Day in Atlanta,
and it was canceled 15 minutes before the show with no explanation.
Let's listen to the audio.
I'm pissed.
Anita ball-headed ass.
They canceled the concert.
Piss, Anita.
Run me my money.
They did get a refund.
Is Anita ball-headed?
I don't appreciate that.
As a member of the ball-headed society,
we don't have nothing to do with none of that.
I did not expect that.
I was like, are you sticking up for Anita?
No, I'm sticking up for myself.
They said that Anita Baker wasn't even in the state.
Anita Baker just don't give a damn.
Like, last year, she was had beefing with baby face.
It's still going on.
Like, this is crazy.
Listen, I hope that everything is okay,
because when they don't make an announcement,
a lot of times you're just like, well, what does that do to?
Like, are they trying to keep something private?
You know, what is that?
But it's pretty clear now that Anita is dropping hints
that she wouldn't make it, okay?
Like, she has a few song titles in her set list
that if we tweak them, you know,
it kind of gives us an idea, right?
Like, the original song is,
Giving you the best that I've got.
The title is more like,
Giving you the very least that I've got.
Original, you bring me joy.
New title, you bring me a refund.
Yes, we need it now.
We are, we are, we are.